oohilove.com 2009-10-16

# Privacy | oohilove

1\. General

Ooh I Love.com.au (hereinafter referred to as "Ooh I Love") is a service provided by Ooh I Love (hereinafter referred to as "Ooh I Love" or "We". We recognize and respect your personal privacy. This Privacy Policy describes all aspects relating to gathering information while you are visiting the Ooh I Love website, how We handle your personal information for our services and all further permissible uses of such information.

By accepting the Privacy Policy and the Terms and Conditions in registration, you expressly consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is effective upon acceptance for new users and is otherwise effective after being posted on the website.

2\. Data Collection

You may use Ooh I Love at any time without registering. When you visit our website, data is saved on our servers in an anonymous format, as is the website that you visit us from, the websites that you proceed to from our site, and your IP address. As this is being done, no personal data is associated with you.

However, we do need some personal information from you so that you can actively participate in Ooh I Love. We would therefore like to request that you agree to the collection and storage of some of your data. You can revoke your consent any time by cancelling your registration.

Once you have registered for "My Ooh I Love", you are asked to choose a Ooh I Love user name together with a password, which then allows you to take advantage of all of the Ooh I Love services.

Personal data is the information needed to identify you, for example your name, address, gender, date of birth, e-mail address, mobile phone number, etc. With your consent, personal data are recorded and processed by Ooh I Love, in particular:

  * When you register with "My Ooh I Love"
  * When you buy bids
  * When you win an auction
  * We will only collect your account or credit card data if this is necessary in order to process payment.

Usage data are personal data that identify the user, as well as information on the Ooh I Love services the user utilizes, for example your Ooh I Love user name together with the associated password and your IP address when you purchase bids or win an auction. We collect these data only to make it possible for you to use Ooh I Love. The data is stored only for as long as it is necessary to process bids you have bought and auctions you have won.

3\. Use of the Data

Personal data such as name, address, etc. are used to process item shipment after an auction is won. We ask for your e-mail address so that we can stay in contact with you by e-mail. We need your account data or credit card data to process payment transactions you are involved with. We also use your personal data to communicate with you regarding orders, to process auctions, marketing retentions and to process other transactions. Similarly, we use your data in order to inform you of marketing promotions or to enable third parties authorized by us to perform technical, logistical, or other services. All data is stored securely on our servers.

4\. Newsletter

PWhen you register with Ooh I Love, you state whether you agree to receive the e-mail newsletter. If you agree, we will use this method to inform you of new functions or promotions on our website. You can revoke this consent anytime by replying to email with subject line remove or by using the corresponding link in the e-mail newsletter at any time.

5\. Forwarding Personal Data to Third Parties

Your personal information may be passed on to third parties only if this is necessary to process a payment transaction or a business transaction with our partners. Essentially, these are respectable businesses that comply with applicable data protection regulations. Ooh I Love will not release any personal information on you or forward this to third parties insofar as you have not given your express consent to do so, or unless we are required to do so by law.

6\. Disclosure of Personal Data

We may disclose personal information to respond to legal requirements, enforce our policies, respond to claims that a listing or other content violates the rights of others, or protect anyone's rights, property, or safety. Such information will be disclosed in accordance with applicable laws and regulations. We may also share your personal information with third parties assisting our business operations under contract, including but not limited to fraud investigations and debt collection, with law enforcement or other governmental officials if required by law, and with other business entities, should we plan to merge with or be acquired by that business entity. Without limiting the above, in an effort to respect your privacy and our ability to keep the community free from bad actors, we will not otherwise disclose your personal information to law enforcement, other government officials, or other third parties without a subpoena, court order or substantially similar legal procedure, except when we believe in good faith that the disclosure of information is necessary to prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss or to report suspected illegal activity.

7\. Viewing/Changing Personal Data

You can view the information in your Ooh I Love account at any time and update it as necessary using your Ooh I Love user name and your Ooh I Love password.

Once we are informed, we will adjust incorrect data accordingly.

We will notify you upon request at any time as to whether and what personal data in respect to your identity or your pseudonym has been stored.

8\. Revoking Consent/Deleting Your Account

Upon your request, we will close your account and remove your personal information from view as soon as reasonably possible, based on your account activity and in accordance with applicable law. We do retain personal information from closed accounts to comply with law, prevent fraud, collect any fees owed, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, enforce our General Terms and Conditions, and take other actions otherwise permitted by law. You can delete or deactivate your Ooh I Love account at any time. When you delete your membership, your personal data is removed from our database unless we are required to save the data.

9\. The Use of Cookies at our Website

Vudu uses so-called "cookies", which are files that are stored on your computer that can be retrieved to assist in customizing your experience with the online service. The information saved supports the functionality of the site, for example by keeping track of your visual preferences or controlling the frequency of "pop-up" windows. These cookies are deleted after one month. You are free to prevent cookies from being saved on your hard drive by adjusting the corresponding settings in your browser. It is not necessary to accept cookies in order to use our service. However, we would like to point out that turning off these settings may result in limited functionality.

10\. Security Measures

The information in your Ooh I Love account and in your Ooh I Love profile is password protected, so that only you have access to this personal information. Please note that you are not permitted to provide your password to anyone else. Ooh I Love will never ask for your password in e-mails that you receive unexpectedly or that you did not request. Please remember to log out of your account and to close your internet browser window when you leave the Ooh I Love site; this is especially important if you use a PC in public locations. At present, this is the safest way to ensure that no one has access to your personal information. We assume no liability for the abuse of login data and passwords used.

11\. Protection from Web Crawlers or Spam

Ooh I Love assures you that we will use your e-mail address with your express consent only for the purposes stated in the Terms of Use. We will not sell your e-mail address to third parties, and we will prevent your e-mail address from being recorded by "web crawlers" or "web spiders" to the best of our ability. If you believe that your e-mail address has been recorded in this way, please let us know immediately.

12\. Data Protection Guidelines Changes

MWe may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the amended terms on this site.
